cloudbric.com 2018-11-08

# Privacy Policy for Cloudbric | Elite Full Service Website Security

This privacy policy is applicable to any and all products, solutions, and services provided by Cloudbric Corporation (“CLOUDBRIC”).

### **Personal Information:**

The term “personal information” means information pertaining to an individual that helps CLOUDBRIC manage customer and potential customer relationships. Information we gather may include:

  *        Your name
  *        Office and/or home address
  *        Email address
  *        Telephone number
  *        Your company’s name and your title
  *        Data of our correspondence with you and information about needs for technical assistance
  *        Transaction history, shipping, billing, and payment information for applicable services (including, but not limited to Cloudbric)
  *        Information regarding your connectivity through your  computer or device operating system (including, but not limited to your browser and IP address)
  *        Other data that may not identify you but helps us to optimize our website for better user experience

### **What do we use the information for?**

The general purpose of gathering this information is to provide users, customers, and participants with useful information regarding CLOUDBRIC’s marketing events, promotions, products, services, solutions, subscriptions, etc. CLOUDBRIC retains this information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined, unless a longer retention period is required by applicable laws.

We may also use the information to:

  *        Communicate with you directly, including if you contact us with an inquiry
  *        Verify your identity and interests in our products and services
  *        Provide support with our services
  *        Deliver monthly or event-based newsletters, and product or technical updates
  *        Allow you to view a limited-access portion of our site
  *        Evaluate our site and optimize it for the best user experience
  *        Collect feedback about our marketing activities and product satisfaction
  *        Secure our applications
  *        Facilitate our services
  *        Provide you with customized sales support
  *        Enforce our legal rights and/or comply with legal requirements
  *        Meet contractual obligations

### **Information to/from Third Parties:**

CLOUDBRIC may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with us to provide products, solutions, and services. Personal information will only be shared by CLOUDBRIC to provide or improve upon the company’s products, services, and advertising. However, if you feel so inclined to unsubscribe from Third Party communications, you may contact us in the manner indicated at the end of this privacy policy, or directly through our contact forms.

Our website may also on occasion link to third parties. This is not an endorsement, authorization, or representation of our affiliation with that third party.

### **Browsers and Cookies**

To provide our customized services and user experience on the website, CLOUDBRIC uses cookies to collect additional website usage data to improve our services. Cookies are small text files of information sent to a browser by a website operating server, and stored on the hard drive of your PC. When you visit a website, cookies are accessed by the server to ensure that your preferences are maintained, allowing for increased efficiency. Cookies also give us information on analytics regarding the interests of visitors.

Please note that third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website. Therefore, we may use your cookies to show you ads on sites across the Internet for remarketing purposes. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

While most browsers allow for cookies, you can also disable cookies through following your browser’s instructions in their settings. Note that some services may not be available if cookies are disabled.

### **Rights of Users in Terms of Personal Information**

Users who have relayed their personal information to CLOUDBRIC may review or change their collected personal information at any time through contacting CLOUDBRIC. They may also request to withdraw consent to CLOUDBRIC and unsubscribe from all services.

Participants are also free to contact CLOUDBRIC’s personal information manager in writing, by phone, or email through the contact information listed below. Once users request to have the information corrected or withdrawn, CLOUDBRIC will not use the information until the request has been fulfilled and personal information has been corrected or removed as requested.

### **Data Retention**

We keep your personal information for as long as necessary for the reasons it was collected. We also keep it to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements.

### **Our Policy Towards Children**

To the best of CLOUDBRIC’s knowledge, we do not focus on or collect information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without the consent of the parent or guardian, he or she should contact us at [support@cloudbric.com](mailto:support@cloudbric.com). If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will remove such information from our database in a timely manner.

### **How We Secure Your Information**

We’re a security company, so we know that personal information is very important. We prioritize safeguarding your information, and utilize proper security measures to protect your information.

  *        We hold our employees to privacy and confidentiality agreements, training and educating them to understand the importance of your information.
  *        We safeguard our facilities and servers to make sure that digital or paper trails are kept safe
  *        We use antivirus software, and web application firewalls to monitor traffic as well as block unnecessary/malicious traffic. We utilize encryption to protect our databases.
  *        We train our personnel to make sure they’re aware of the importance of web and data security, and keep up-to-date on policies to which we are held accountable.

### **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Information is always changing, and so are policies. CLOUDBRIC may update its policy from time to time, and when the policy is changed, we will put up a notice on the website, letting you know.

### **Contact**

Users may contact us at any time. We also provide you with opportunities to opt-out or request for a removal of your personal information. To exercise those rights, feel free to contact us. Also contact us with any questions or concerns regarding the privacy practices via writing or email.

Cloudbric Corporation.  
16F, 25 Gukjegeumyung-ro 2-gil,  
Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea 07327

Attn: Cloudbric Webmaster  
Email: support@cloudbric.com

### **Effective Date / Update:**

This privacy policy was last updated on January 2, 2018.  
_Note: Adherence to the “safe harbor” frameworks has been removed from this Privacy Policy in 2017 as it is no longer a valid mechanism for complying with EU data protection requirements._
